[
    {
        "id":1,
        "front": "apple",
        "back": "яблоко",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "red",
        "back": "красный",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "lion",
        "back": "лев",
        "setName": "Animals"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "dog",
        "back":"собака",
        "setName": "Animals"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "toyota",
        "back": "тойота",
        "setName": "Cars"
    },
    {
        "id": 6, 
        "front": "lexus",
        "back": "лексус",
        "setName": "Cars"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front":"ford",
        "back":"форд",
        "setName": "Cars"
    },
    {
        "id":8,
        "front": "nissan",
        "back": "ниссан",
        "setName": "Cars"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "padding",
        "back": "отступ внутренний",
        "setName": "Css-свойства"
    },
    {
        "id":10,
        "front": "ice hockey",
        "back": "хоккей",
        "setName": "Sport"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "front":"margin",
        "back":"отступ внешний", 
        "setName": "Css-свойства"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "front": "margin",
        "back":"отступ внешний",
        "setName": "Css-свойства"
    }
]